<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<docParts>
    <part id="OldSortOrder">
        <remarks>
            <para>Sort order is consistent with precedence order, but provides an order for versions
            with the same precedence. Sort order is determined by comparing the major, minor,
            patch, prerelease, and build metadata portions in order from left to right. The major,
            minor, and patch versions are compared numerically. A prerelease version precedes a release
            version.</para>
            <para>The prerelease portion is compared by comparing each prerelease identifier from
            left to right. Numeric prerelease identifiers proceed alphanumeric identifiers. Numeric
            identifiers are compared numerically. Alphanumeric identifiers are compared lexically
            in ASCII sort order. A longer series of prerelease identifiers follows a shorter series
            if all the preceding identifiers are equal.</para>
            <para>Otherwise equal versions without build metadata precede those with metadata. The
            build metadata is compared by comparing each metadata identifier. Numeric identifiers
            are compared numerically. Alphanumeric identifiers are compared lexically in ASCII sort
            order. A longer series of metadata identifiers follows a shorter series if all the
            preceding identifiers are equal.</para>
        </remarks>
    </part>
    <part id="CompareToReturns">
        <returns>
            An integer that indicates whether this instance precedes, follows, or is equal to
            the other in the sort order.
            <list type="table">
                <listheader>
                    <term>Value</term>
                    <description>Condition</description>
                </listheader>
                <item>
                    <term>Less than zero</term>
                    <description>This instance precedes the other in the sort order.</description>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <term>Zero</term>
                    <description>This instance is equal to the other.</description>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <term>Greater than zero</term>
                    <description>
                        This instance follows the other in the sort order
                        or the other is <see langword="null" />.
                    </description>
                </item>
            </list>
        </returns>
    </part>
</docParts>